When the days are cold
當日子是冰冷的
And the cards all fold
手上的牌也已成局
And the saints we see
那些我們看到的聖人
Are all made of gold
全是黃金打造的
When your dreams all fail
當你的夢都成空
And the ones we hail
而那些我們擁立的
Are the worst of all
原來都是最壞的
And the blood’s run stale
血只能變得汙濁
I want to hide the truth
我想隱藏事實
I want to shelter you
我想保護你
But with the beast inside
但我深知
There’s nowhere we can hide
我們沒有地方可以躲藏
No matter what we breed
不管我們是什麼種族
We still are made of greed
我們都是貪婪做的
This is my kingdom come
這就是我
When you feel my heat
當你感到我的溫度
Look into my eyes
看進我的眼
It’s where my demons hide
那裡就是我隱藏邪惡的地方
Don’t get too close
別靠得太近
It’s dark inside
裡面很黑暗
It’s where my demons hide
那裡就是我隱藏邪惡的地方
When the curtain’s call
當布幕降下
Is the last of all
最後的時候到了
When the lights fade out
當燈光熄滅
All the sinners crawl
所有的罪人蠢動
So they dug your grave
他們挖開你的墳
And the masquerade
並且這些人
Will come calling out
不斷的指責
At the mess you made
你所製造的一切混亂
Don’t want to let you down
不想讓你失望
But I am hell bound
但我身陷地獄
Though this is all for you
雖然一切都是為了你
Don’t want to hide the truth
我不想隱藏事實
No matter what we breed
不管我們是什麼種族
We still are made of greed
我們始終是貪婪做的
This is my kingdom come
這是我
When you feel my heat
當你感受我的餘溫
Look into my eyes
看著我的眼底深處
It’s where my demons hide
那裡就是我隱藏邪惡的地方
Don’t get too close
所以 請你不要再走近我
It’s dark inside
這裡只有無盡的不幸
It’s where my demons hide
那裡就是我隱藏邪惡的地方
They say it's what you make
他們說一切取決於你
I say it's up to fate
我說其實取決於命運
It's woven in my soul
它已織進我的靈魂
I need to let you go
我得讓你走
Your eyes, they shine so bright
你的雙眼閃得如此明亮
I want to save their light
我想留住那些亮光
I can't escape this now
如今我已無法逃脫
Unless you show me how
除非你能指引我
When you feel my heat
當你感受我的餘溫
Look into my eyes
看著我的眼底深處
It’s where my demons hide
那裡就是我隱藏邪惡的地方
Don’t get too close
所以 請你不要再走近我
It’s dark inside
這裡只有無盡的不幸
It’s where my demons hide
那裡就是我隱藏邪惡的地方
那貪婪的心魔